Chune!
Chune…
I forgot about the doctor's appointment.
See you soon.
What the…
Capets
This is how I think since childhood.
There is a certain amount of happiness in life.
Not bad.
What?
But what is it?
Well, let it.
It doesn't matter if it takes you where you need to go.
In other words,
there is a certain amount of unhappiness.
What? What's going on?
It can't be!
No. go
COOKED CORN
Everything is simple.
If someone is going through a series of difficulties,
one can hope
that something good will happen soon.
And let I was hungry anyway.
I will eat corn and rest.
Where did you find this old can?
It will continue to break.
Get rid of this car and buy a new one.
Will still serve.
Can you check the wipers?
They turn on when they want.
I will be grateful if you fix it.
And now what?
STONES ARE FALLING
THE ROAD IS CLOSED
ROUTE 101 DEtour
So what? Lately
I don't do much sports.
It's like self-suggestion, and it works.
CHEONHYE MEMORIAL PARK
If I didn't think so,
I probably wouldn't be able to stand it.
I'm alone again.
Did you have a fight with Chun?
It seems he doesn't want to see you
because you made him suffer.
When my life hit rock bottom...
I would have easily given up if it weren't for that.
I'll go now.
I probably won't come either.
To be honest, I don't remember much.
I have nothing to say.
Chun and I are fine.
Don't worry about us.
That's why I decided to believe it.
It's time for something good.
What the…
This is the day today.
Such
What? Why is it not working again?
God
This is…
What's wrong?
How…
what are you doing here
Need to fix something?
If you have experienced difficulties...
hold on
- You...
- Why is this...
…it means that only happiness is ahead.
You fixed it.
It looks like that.
EPISODE 4
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT
What is your goal, Mr. Ko?
Are you interested in fame or money?
Recently your articles
the most popular in our magazine.
Your texts are quite cynical.
Easy to read, but sharp,
they are listened to.
Want to become a famous critic?
A famous critic? Is there such a position?
I can help.
You can become the main critic of the magazine.
It's time for fresh faces.
I thought a critic's job was to write reviews.
We can take you to the media space.
That is, on television,
YouTube and radio programs,
you will be the most beautiful
modern film critic.
Not like blogger Goddam,
and as Ko Geum, a film critic.
But I like it as it is.
Then more people will read
your articles and will trust your opinion.
You will have more influence.
And of course, you will earn more.
As far as?
Lot.
A lot…
This is a great opportunity for you.
Work as conscientiously as
but I am open to something more provocative.
What movie is next?
I plan to watch a new movie
directed by Koo Yeon-sik.
THE YOUNG DIRECTOR WANTS UNIVERSALITY
And he writes well.
No, it's all me.
I gave him good answers to work with.
I knew that. He writes reviews
for all films except mine.
Think you're that cool?
The movie is really not about me.
"TWO SEASONS"
Did I come early?
Maybe he's still sleeping.
He scared me!
Where did he go so early?
who are you
Didn't I come there?
I must have made a mistake.
Be there.
Who was it?
I don't mind. They made a mistake with the address.
- When did you arrive?
- Just now.
where have you been all morning
I fell asleep while waiting.
I went to the cinema.
You've never done this before.
No inspiration to write songs?
I liked the last song.
can i sing
listen
You don't need to take care of me.
didn't think
that your confidence will be shaken.
I liked you more
when he was arrogant for no reason.
Get up. Let's go record a song.
Are you a fanatic?
A fanatic in free fall.
Enough to consider. Let's play games.
- Can I borrow some books?
- Of course.
Or you can read here
and stay the night.
Not at all.
Sir, do you have a daughter?
And what? I don't look like someone who has a family?
you never talked about your family
so i thought
that you are a fanatic who lives alone.
This is also true.
Do you live separately?
Who wants to live with me
when I'm constantly shooting movies?
I'm miserable.
It's hard to be miserable
sitting in an expensive massage chair.
Things are worthless.
Live life wisely.
By the way, why don't you write anything
on your blog?
I liked the older posts better.
Professionals write when they are paid.
And this is a professional review?
Your latest reviews are borderline.
Aren't you too sharp?
I'm only harsh with bad movies
and not with the good ones.
Film critics and directors -
mortal enemies.
Don't make your enemies hate you
even more It's tiring.
We are just doing our job.
Don't take it personally.
When dealing with people
not everything is so simple.
What do you have there?
My brother loves them.
How do I get them home?
It would be much easier
if someone else were here.
Do you want to kick me out of my own house?
Sir, maybe next time
bring your brother here?
Anyway, whatever.
When you talk about him, you are like a child.
OK, I'll stay with you for another two hours.
Yes!
- Get up.
- Yes!
OK.
We need to close the blinds.
ESSENTIAL REVIEWS OF MR. GODAM
There is more and more arrogance in his texts.
OK.
Song Chu Ah is already leaving.
When she arrives, take her to the conference room.
Good.
An invitation has been sent
for a preview.
I don't know if I will have time.
Whose movie?
Directed by Koo Yeon Sik.
Truth?
CONFERENCE HALL AND LOUNGE
I agree to make a movie.
Can you really make it?
I don't know, but it's worth a try.
And that's all?
The script reminds me of "La La Land"
and even Start Again.
And "The Birth of a Star" comes to mind.
Is it a mixture of everything?
But it's an original story, and that's what matters.
Universal, but unfamiliar.
Stories about love and achieving dreams
sell well.
You need a better reason
to make a movie?
Your vision is too simplistic
I am worried
you already know
that this story is important to me
I hope you will turn it into a good movie.
Even a heartwarming story
may fail
and the story that does not care
could be a hit.
I promise nothing.
Our visions do not coincide.
Do you know that music is very important?
I know
Can I advise you?
It is possible, but I will decide.
Good.
Why is it so difficult for this family
get together for lunch on the weekend?
Everyone is very busy.
Is there a lot of work at the hospital?
I have everything as usual. What about you?
He has been busy lately
clinical trials.
- At what stage are you?
- The third.
It's almost over.
take it
take away I don't need to.
Si Chun.
Mom and Dad waited a long time.
come back home
- I will take care of myself.
- Obviously not.
You yourself said that music is just a hobby.
And you gave up everything to live like this?
You think you are very cool
in your 20s?
Give up everything for music -
it's a bit selfish.
But you didn't give up everything.
- What?
- Tell me, what did you give up?
Mom pays for the studio rent.
When you come home for lunch
they give you money
you do whatever you want
because you have somewhere to return to.
You should have achieved something by now.
And if you haven't achieved anything yet...
Xi Chun, how much more do we have
blindly believe in you?
Brother
What faith are you talking about?
What?
Has anyone ever believed in me?
It's really you!
what are you doing
I don't think this is my place.
sit down They're about to start.
Thanks for coming to the preview.
I'm Yoo Yong Hyun and I will…
We are watching a movie together for the second time.
...you will meet
with director Koo Yeon-sik and the cast.
Congratulations. I'm Koo Yeon-sik, the director of this movie.
The movie is… not too serious and not deep.
My movies are rather…
Thank you
Shall we have dinner?
I showed you indulgence
but don't act like it.
What's wrong with the family having dinner together?
what family
Neighbors are like family.
Don't talk nonsense and stay away.
Got it?
Good for you!
He accepted it too quickly.
Something wrong?
What happened?
You can not say.
San Siku,
how many years have I been working here?
Let's count.
Six years...
Are you going to ask for more money again?
I gave you a big bonus last time.
are you serious
It was supposed to be a temporary job.
And already so long?
Are you having problems now?
I think…
that I'm miserable
Don't call yourself pathetic.
You thought it was easy to be an artist?
I'll take out the trash for you today.
I think you're fine.
- You are well done.
- What uncle?
- Enough.
- Look at yourself.
A sad face does not suit you.
Let's drink something with ice.
Good?
- Of course.
- Make drinks.
Listen, Honsey.
A blind date. I forgot about the date!
What?
You can pack up and go home.
I will go first.
I thought we would have a drink.
drink whatever
just close the door when you leave. bye
Seriously?
A blind date, anyway.
What's the rush? Forgot something?
Will you drink with me?
Don't you want to drink with me?
No, I don't want to spoil the drink.
I asked to pass by.
why did you come
The last meeting was unexpected,
and we didn't have a chance to talk...
Get to the point.
do you want me back
Do you want to be friends?
Hong Si Chun.
I'm against it.
Got it?
Now go.
You don't listen as usual. It's annoying.
Five years ago I was screaming and crying
and begged to take me back
or at least stay friends.
You are the same now as you were then.
- You are not the only one who suffered.
- Yes, of course.
But what is the point in this?
I don't feel anything for you.
And if that's not why I'm here?
I'm not here to
to get you back or be friends
What?
I wrote about us.
What did you write?
As you said, I was desperate
and drew inspiration everywhere.
I wrote about us.
I want to make a movie, but I need you.
I believed in you these seven years so
like no other.
I loved your music more than anyone
and now I need it.
I really need your music.
Did you get to the hospital without any problems?
Yes, of course.
Probably overworked a little. Shoulders hurt.
Really? i thought
the appointment was yesterday, not today.
Yes. I was there yesterday.
It still hurts since yesterday.
It was today.
Chun, I got a call from the hospital today.
They say you're late
you don't come and it's strange
because you said you went there
when I went to visit my parents.
Simple
I felt bad
and went for a walk around the block...
Think you've recovered?
It's hard for you to even walk.
Why are you missing sessions?
I'm better now. And you know it.
In this condition
just walking is enough...
Are you a doctor now?
Who said you decide?
Treatment is too expensive.
I don't care. Continue
What do you care?
I am invited to various shows,
and my earnings increased significantly.
Expensive, yes.
I can pay double or triple
so don't miss it.
Good, good.
You just raised your voice at me
because you are the breadwinner now?
Sadly.
When I got the call, I thought:
"It sounds like a teacher calling from school."
Do not miss sessions.
I heard you.
I have high hopes
on the Korean film industry.
Take Kim Yoo Chin's new movie...
What?
- The film is good.
- What is he doing?
It was a positive view...
It's amazing. What is he, a celebrity?
Why is he on TV?
I saw this young man somewhere.
Does he live opposite?
Is he famous?
Absolutely not.
Anyone is invited to these shows.
I can go too.
He can speak.
You can't do that.
What-what?
What are you saying?
I can do much better than him!
But this is part of my work as a critic.
What does he drink?
Instead of being condescending
to new directors,
we must tell the truth,
so that they don't relax
and shot the best films...
- Hello.
What is it?
Greetings.
I see if this critic
recommended your movie.
And what? Is the movie on the list?
No, there isn't.
I wouldn't waste time on a list
which is not trusted.
But he is quite popular among young people.
Really?
LIVE: INTERVIEW
WITH THE YOUNG CRITIC KO GYOM
Why is he everywhere all of a sudden?
"We must love each other".
This is a new film directed by Lee Ru Ri.
I would describe this film in one word -
"lightness".
My boy! He can speak.
He is literally everywhere. What's going on?
He always craved attention.
But he deserved it
unlike some…
They ask me if I'm single
from birth, because I write harsh reviews.
No, it's not like that.
it hurts more
when you tiptoe next to me
Tiptoe? I?
Of course. What nonsense.
I see right through you
how then
when you pushed Chu Ah into the bar and left.
What? Did I push Chu Ah and leave?
Never.
What were you talking about?
She wants to work with me.
Work? That is?
She asked me to write music for the script.
This girl is something.
Coldness blows from her.
Am I really that pathetic?
Is that why she's offering me a job?
You are exaggerating again.
You are too negative about everything.
Maybe she is genuinely interested
in work with you
Maybe she thought about it for a long time.
Indifferently.
I have not the slightest intention
stand between you
What should I do with you, handsome?
This is your character.
You two…
No, I will be silent.
Wipe the glasses. Time to open up.
God!
can i come in
Of course.
And what did your ex say? Did he agree?
He looked at me like I was crazy and left.
You look I would do the same.
It was necessary to say it differently.
How to convince him?
Does it have to be his music?
I wrote the script thinking about him.
What if I don't like it?
You will like it.
You are too confident.
His time just hasn't come yet.
I know he will succeed
as a songwriter.
Does he know that you believe in him so much?
That's the problem.
Now people don't communicate.
Are you sure you don't have feelings for him?
It would make the job more difficult.
I have no feelings.
I can say the same about him.
He seems to have a girlfriend.
That's good.
You got rid of that boy
which got on your nerves?
Did you get rid of it? No.
He becomes even more clingy, so I…
Did I tell you?
What?
We shared a lot
civil servant Kim.
Apparently, she said everything
for free Pilates classes.
So what? say
Not today.
Tell me! I will give you
free pilates lessons.
As? You are not a pilates instructor.
I will teach Do you want me to teach you?
Well, I…
Do you want it or not?
The whole town is talking about him.
Greet film critic Ko Gyom.
Greetings, I'm Ko Gyum.
Your articles are attention grabbing.
You harshly criticized Koo Yeon Sik's film.
Are you ready for the consequences?
I am responsible for every written word.
What disappointed you the most about the film?
Sir, can you turn up the volume?
Of course.
I don't care how the movie ends:
happy or sad.
But convert the film
with such a vague ending
as a means of educating the audience -
it's irresponsible.
A rude remark.
I understand why you are called
"public critic"...
FILM CRITIC KO GYOM
…and why the public loves you.
I believe that the critic is obliged
write accurate reviews for viewers.
I write critical reviews,
but I also talk about good cinema,
which could not be noticed,
because it is not considered entertaining.
It is a sword sharpened at both ends,
but critics are needed by those
who makes movies, otherwise...
It is dangerous.
I said.
You have achieved success very quickly.
I don't care about success.
Will I now have more orders?
You should attend more events
as long as people are interested.
You are eloquent.
You have more stardom than I thought.
Don't stop there.
Of course.
I will take my stardom and leave.
Since when are you so busy?
You are literally everywhere.
I don't like it, but I have to, because they invite me.
Of course. You like attention.
I get paid well.
I will tolerate unwanted attention.
Of course. Make money my friend.
You've been kind of sad lately.
Problems with writing music?
Just…
I knew I was miserable
but made sure once more.
did you know
Chu Ah started writing scripts,
and they even made a movie.
You used to hang out on film sets,
and now you earn from it.
And me?
what am i doing
Time to give up?
When I started writing music, I thought
what will i know
do I have a knack and when should I quit everything?
But this ship has sailed.
Now I'm a fool who doesn't realize
that is not capable of anything.
What a shame.
Are you crying?
Thank God. Because it became almost embarrassing.
Stop talking stupid and drink.
You said it yourself.
Enough bullshit, just do your thing.
Everyone has their own breakthrough.
And you were always the best of us.
I do not object.
Cheers.
25TH FRAME
How did it happen?
Such Is he all right?
I don't know.
Are we not responsible?
And don't say!
This is how the day begins.
DIRECTOR KU YON SIK WAS SAVED BY FAMILY
AFTER AN OVERDOSE OF SLEEPING AIDS
KOO YOUNG SIK IN THE HOSPITAL
AFTER THE SUICIDE ATTEMPT
I'm sorry With the director
Is Koo Young Sik ok?
Sort of. His stomach was washed.
He is in the ward.
Where to find it?
Do you know each other?
A minute
This is the critic!
Who is Gyom?
It's him!
- Yes!
- Why are you here?
- Do you feel guilty?
- What do you feel?
- Did you come to apologize?
- Is it true?
- Say something.
- Even a word!
are you sorry
How are you feeling?
Do you think it was because of your review?
- Do you feel sorry for him?
- Say something.
Don't do it here.
My dad needs some rest, you better go.
go You are only making it worse.
OK.
What?
- Is he really leaving?
- What? Mr. Ko, wait a minute!
- Wait!
- Mr. Ko!
THE LINE BETWEEN CRITICISM AND PRIDE
ARE CRITICS ALWAYS RIGHT?
I KNEW THAT
INSULTS ARE NOT CRITICISM
MUST BE HUMBLE
I HAVE ALWAYS HATED HIM
FREEDOM OF SPEECH? FUNNY
CAN CRITICS BE INSULTED?
Here.
Everything is fine.
Why did you go there?
and threw the brush into the fire?
I would rather sit quietly.
I don't know. I didn't think then.
That's right. I said be careful
critics are easy targets.
Director Ku will be fine.
Don't worry.
I guess you already understood.
People don't care when you praise a movie.
But when you say that the movie is a failure,
they flock like flies to honey.
People hide behind critics like you
to shame movies.
And when this happens, they turn away
and looking for a scapegoat.
So don't worry too much.
- Everything is fine with me.
- Are you sure?
Don't read those comments.
There is no need.
My inbox is already full.
Ignore them. Clear?
- Come in!
- Director Kim. Here!
Did you call someone?
I agreed with her first.
And I invited you to comfort you.
You already know each other. The bigger the merrier.
Sit down, director Kim. Beer?
A bottle of beer, please!
What beer?
Any that don't sell well.
Here.
They write about me that I betrayed my country.
- What is it with people?
- Director Ma!
Park Chun Tae! You are still alive.
- Long time no see.
- Yes.
Where did you disappear?
My film was a flop, so I went to bed.
Don't say that. Drink with us.
No, I'm not alone. Another time.
Really? OK.
do you still smoke Let's go smoke.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
Come on.
- Did you drink a lot?
- Yes.
Is everything good?
And what?
You fry yourself.
Help?
Everything is fine. I am an expert in this.
- Well...
- Are you the critic?
It's you. I'm Kim Yong Woo. Do you remember me?
You wrote a review of my film.
You are the director of the film "Balcony".
Do you remember!
- Of course.
- Really?
Would you like to go for a drink?
do i want a drink
Thank you, I'm not in the mood.
You are funny.
Unbelievable.
You made me look like an idiot
and now offer a drink?
Didn't like my review?
You offended me for no reason.
So what do you think?
You are something.
I guess you have to be cheeky
to write such nonsense.
And…
you drink after
what happened to Mr. Ku?
If he doesn't survive,
it will be on your conscience.
what are you doing Get up.
who are you
None of your business. Get up. Immediately.
You didn't have to listen to him.
It must be difficult for you because of this.
He behaved rudely.
Why is it difficult for me?
What?
Why should it be difficult for me?
I didn't do anything wrong.
It is not my fault that the film is a failure.
Not all movies are successful.
We all experience failures.
It's not in the movie. An injured person.
I know, and I say that it is not my fault.
It's not my fault.
Koh Gome.
I didn't say it was your fault.
People who say that
just looking for the culprit.
Are you of the same opinion?
Do you always twist things?
Do you still want to teach me something?
Kim Mubi.
I am comforting you, not teaching you.
I sympathize, not criticize.
you didn't notice
that Mr. Ma and I were around, taking care of you?
You can pretend it doesn't hurt,
but don't ignore those around you.
You know what pissed me off
when did i meet you again
You only cared about your pain like now.
You are not interested in other people.
VIDE BAR
ok
Let's work together.
I'm betting everything.
And what exactly?
His pride.
Pride that did not want
help from the person I loved.
Si Chun.
I will write something grandiose.
Better than yours.
Mom, I'm leaving.
take this
Good.
KOO YOUNG SIK
You are Mubi, right?
It's okay, don't get up.
You haven't changed.
And you have grown old.
Truth?
Your mother was talking about you.
I was proud that you became a director.
I liked your movie.
Hong Tong would be delighted.
why did you come
What happened to you?
You really…
Everything was wrong.
Journalists twisted everything.
Truth?
I have been for a long time
I can't fall asleep without sleeping pills.
And I have anxiety problems.
I had too much to drink that night
and took pills...
I didn't know it would happen like this.
This job really demands a person
physical and mental health.
are you ok
You have to take care of your health.
I take care of my health to prove
that you can do it without harming yourself.
Your dad always showed you off.
He said you are smart.
If something happened to you,
I would hate the movie.
Why does cinema make people like this?
God I am ashamed.
You must call and start a new project.
I love your movies since childhood.
OK. Thank you.
Rest, I'll go.
I would like to rest
but that guy is restless.
I say it's fine
but he comes every day.
what are you doing here
I'm just waiting.
For what?
For something good to happen again.
And you came again.
I don't want to admit it...
but my weakness is
that I open my heart easily
for the small and unfortunate.
I'm tired.
Yes.
me too
And I'm afraid that Ko Geum is one of those.
LIKE IN THE MOVIE
I'm not too happy,
that Kim Mubi is happiness,
which comes after misfortune.
Because next time and in the future...
Where did he disappear to?
How so? He could wake me up.
I can't believe that he left me.
You scared me.
What is it? I thought you left.
And you don't have to scare people like that.
I thought you were cold, so I went to get a blanket.
You would let me sleep here
and did not send home?
your truth Why didn't I think of that?
I will go
Don't be so pathetic, go home already.
It's annoying.
Mubi.
Did I allow you to call me by my name?
…hope it will always be like that.
I want to…
to like you again
Translation of subtitles: Natalya Kovalyshyn